Finding Aid for the Sierra Club Angeles Chapter Records LSC.1199
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Newsletters
  - Desert Peaks Section
    - The Desert Sage (No. 52 - 1), 1950 - 1965 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - The Desert Sage (No. 241 - 233), 1994 - 1996 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - The Desert Sage (No. 232 - 211) (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - The Desert Sage (No. 210 - 189), 1987 - 1990 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - The Desert Sage (No. 185 - 157), 1981 - 1986 (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - The Desert Sage (No. 156 - 133) (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - The Desert Sage (No. 132 - 107) (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - The Desert Sage (No. 105 - 80), 1965 - 1970 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - The Desert Sage (No. 79 - 56), 1951 - 1964 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - The Desert Sage (No. 55 - 2) (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - The Desert Sage (No. 324 - 313) (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - The Desert Sage (No. 317 - 312), 2007 - 2008 (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - The Desert Sage (No. 311 - 299), 2005 - 2007 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - The Desert Sage (No. 298 - 283) (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - The Desert Sage (No. 282 - 270) (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - Friends of the Angeles Chapter
    - America's Environmental Crossroads (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - Gay & Lesbian Sierrans and Their Friends
    - Tracks, July/August 1991 (Box 153, Folder 4)
      Not comprehensive, missing issues from years of 1991, 1993 and 1994
  - Hundred Peaks Section
    - Lookout, January/February 1991 - September/October 1992, January/February 1994 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - International Community Section
    - Sierran International (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - K9 Committee (The)
    - Waggin' Trails, [November 1993 - January 1994], [March 1994 - April 1994] (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Legal Advisory Committee Chapter
    - LAC Quarterly News, Summer 1993 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - Little Hiker's Committee
    - Tiny Trailblazer (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Long Beach Group
    - Tidelines, September 1991 - February 1994 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Los Serranos Section
    - Sierra Singles, August 1991 - November 1992 (Box 151, Folder 2)
      Legal size; not comprehensive, only a few issues from each year
  - Mt. Baldy Group
    - Baldy Eagle (The) (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - National Coastal and Marine Committees
    - Log (The), Fall 1993 (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - Nordic Ski Touring Section
    - Snowflake, November 1991 - March 1994 (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - Orange County Section
    - Santiago! (Box 150, Folder 10)
      Missing September/October 1992, and Summer 1993
  - Orange County Sierra Singles
    - Orange Peal, July 1991 - January 1994 (Box 150, Folder 2)
      Missing a few issues from each year
  - Palos Verdes - South Bay Group
    - Foggy View, 1992 (Box 149, Folder 4)
      Duplicate issues of September 1992
  - Pasadena Group
    - Arroyo View, June/July 1991 - February/March 1994 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Recreational Outdoor Accessibility for the Disabled
    - Road Committee (The) (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - River Touring Section
    - Current (The), July 1991 - March 1994 (Box 148, Folder 6)
      Missing issues from June/July/August 1993
  - San Fernando Valley Group
    - Vall-E-Vents (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Santa Ana Mountains Section
    - Trail Builder News, November 1991, September 1992, July 1993, December 1993 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Sierra Peaks Section
    - Echo, July/August 1991 - January/February 1994 (Box 149, Folder 8)
      Not comprehensive, only a few issues from each year from 1991 - 1994
    - Echo Vol. 39 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Echo Vol. 33 - Vol. 38 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Echo Vol. 27 - Vol. 32, [3-4/1983] - [12/1988] (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Echo Vol. 20 - Vol. 26, [1-2/1976] - [11-12/1982] (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Echo Vol. 15 - Vol. 19 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Echo Vol. 1 - Vol. 7, [2/1957] - [11-12/1963] (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Echo Vol. 8 - Vol. 14, [1-2/1964] - [12/1970] (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Echo Vol. 40 - Vol. 50, 2000-2001 (Box 222)
    - Echo Vol. 51 - Vol. 57, 2007-2012 (Box 223, Folders 1-7)
  - Sierra Singles Section
    - Sole Talk (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Sierra Student Coalition
    - Student Activist (The), December 1991, January 1994 (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - Ski Mountaineers and Rock Climbing Section
    - Mugelnoos, October 1991 - March 1994 (Box 150, Folder 1)
      No issues during the summer because of lack of skiiing news
    - Mugelnoos (Box 151, Folder 3)
      Legal size; issue No. 368
  - Verdugo Hills Section
    - Verdugo Views, July/August 1991 - September/October 1992, January/February 1993, January/February 1994 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - West L.A. Section
    - Sierra West, July 1991 - March 1994 (Box 150, Folder 6)
      Missing one or two issues from each year
  - Wilderness Adventures Section
    - Avenues, June/July 1991 - February/March 1994 (Box 148, Folder 2)
- Non-Angeles Chapter Schedules
  - Loma Prieta Chapter, no. 113., 1970 - 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Club de Exploraciones de Mexico, 1969-1970. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Mother Lode Chapter, no.70. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - San Francisco Bay Chapter, nos. 136, 143, 162, 164, 169-174, 177-178., 1956-1970 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Non-Club Associated Mountaineering Organizations
  - The Mountaineer, late 1960s issue (Seattle Mountaineers) (Box 145)
  - Western Outdoor Annuals, 1970s (Federation of Western Outdoor Clubs). (Box 145)
  - Yeti Yells (Box 145)
  - The Wild Cascades, late 1960s issues. (Box 145)
- Nuclear Energy
  - 21/67-68. (Box 106, Folder 3-8)
  - 21/69a-69d. (Box 107, Folder 1-7)
  - 21/69e-72. (Box 108, Folder 1-6)
  - 21/73-77. (Box 109, Folder 1-9)
    Mostly Prop 15.
  - 21/78-82. Social consequences. (Box 110, Folder 1-7)
  - 21/82-89. Various. (Box 111, Folder 1-5)
- Office Records
  - Angeles Chapter
    - Feral Burro Policy (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Membership Committee, 1957 - 1962 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Leadership Reference Books editions 1-9, 1973-1983 (Box 212, Folders 1-4)
    - Leadership Reference Books editions 10-17, 1984-2009 (Box 213, Folders 1-3)
  - Desert Peaks Section
    - Official Desert Peaks Section Records for Sierra Club Newsletter (Box 155, Folder 1)
      From the Desert Peaks Archive for Sage, Volume I
    - Official Desert Peaks Section Records for Sierra Club Newsletter (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Treasures from the DPS Scrapbook, Miscellaneous (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - DPS Bylaws & Scrapbook, 1940s - 1960s (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - Membership Direcotry
    - Directory of Membership and Dues, 1941, 1942, 1946, 1947 (Box 153, Folder 19)
  - Membership Directory
    - Directory of Membership and Dues, 1950 - 1973 (Box 154, Folder 1)
      Not comprehensive, not every year is covered
    - Directory of Membership and Dues (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Directory Sierra Club Mailing List, 1960 - 1969 (Box 154, Folder 3)
      Includes addresses, dues, and organization positions at each of their branches
    - Directory Sierra Club Mailing List (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Mountain Patrols
    - General Correspondence (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Field Reports, 1943 - 1944 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Memorandum, 1942 - 1943 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Maps (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Questionnaires (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1940 - 1947 (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Bulletins of the National Ski Association of America, 1940 - 1949 (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Bulletins of the National Ski Association of America, California Division, 1940 - 1949 (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence with the National Ski Association of America, California Division, 1940 - 1949 (Box 157, Folder 12)
    - Memorandum of the National Ski Patrol System, California Division, 1940 - 1949 (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous from the National Ski Patrol System, 1943 - 1944 (Box 157, Folder 14)
  - Project Flash
    - Miscellaneous (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1972 - 1976 (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Financial Reports, 1971 - 1979 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Average Daily Production (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Bouquet of Roses (Box 156, Folder 9)
      Roses were sent to various congressional members who had voted in favor of F76, which prohibited stripmining in National Park and Monuments
    - Monthly and cumulative records, 1969 - 1972 (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Monthly and cumulative records, 1973 - 1978 (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Operation Feedback, 1976 - 1979 (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Monthly Flashes (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Monthly Flashes (II), 1976 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Quarterly Production Summary and miscellaneous, [1972 - 1975] - [1976 - 1977] (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Sierra Peaks
    - Correspondence (A) (1 of 2), 1975 - 1998 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (A) (2 of 2) (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (B) (1 of 4), 1983 - 1997 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (B) (2 of 4), 1975 - 1987 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (B) (3 of 4) (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (B) (4 of 4) (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (C) (1 of 2), 1979 - 1997 (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (C) (2 of 2), 1955 - 1979 (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (D) (1 of 2) (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (D) (2 of 2) (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (E) (1 of 2), 1984 - 1998 (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (E) (2 of 2), 1957 - 1981 (Box 158, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (F) (1 of 2) (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (F) (2 of 2) (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (G) (1 of 2), 1981 - 1998 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (G) (2 of 2), 1955 - 1981 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (H) (1 of 4) (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (H) (2 of 4) (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (H) (3 of 4), 1972 - 1977 (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (H) (4 of 4), 1955 - 1971 (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (IJ) (1 of 2) (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (IJ) (2 of 2) (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (K) (1 of 2), 1981 - 1997 (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (K) (2 of 2), 1955 - 1980 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (L) (1 of 2) (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (L) (2 of 2) (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (M) (1 of 4), 1995 - 1998 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (M) (2 of 4), 1979 - 1994 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (M) (3 of 4) (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (M) (4 of 4) (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (N), 1956 - 1998 (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (O), 1956 - 1998 (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (PQ) (1 of 2) (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (PQ) (2 of 2) (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (R) (1 of 2), 1980 - 1997 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (R) (2 of 2), 1957 - 1979 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (S) (1 of 4) (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (S) (2 of 4) (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (S) (3 of 4), 1975 - 1986 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (S) (4 of 4), 1955 - 1975 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (T) (1 of 2) (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (T) (2 of 2) (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (UV), 1959 - 1995 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (W) (1 of 2), 1979 - 1994 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (W) (2 of 2) (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (XYZ) (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - SPS Bylaws (Original), November 1986 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Certificate of Appreciation, June 5, 1993 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Official Correspondence (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Echoes from the Past (1 of 2) (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - Echoes from the Past (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Leader Packages, 1961 -1976 (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - Lists and Regulations (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - SPS and CMC Remembrance of D. Dykeman (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - Scrapbook (1 of 4), 1985 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (2 of 4), 1956 - 1959 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (3 of 4) (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (4 of 4) (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - SPS Membership Lists, 1982 - 1984 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - SPS Membership Lists, 1973 - 1977 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - SPS Membership Lists (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - SPS Member and Emblem Lists (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - SPS Membership Reports, 1982 - 1997 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Peaks List History, 1955 - 1986 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - SPS Minutes of Meetings (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - SPS Minutes of Meetings (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - SPS Minutes (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - SPS Minutes, [9/9/1998] - [2/11/1998] (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - SPS Banquet Records (1 of 2), 1980 - 1998 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - SPS Banquet Records (2 of 2) (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Banquet Records (1 of 4), 1994 - 1999 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Banquet Records (2 of 4), 1988 - 1989 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Banquet Records (3 of 4) (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Banquet Records (4 of 4) (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Management Notebook (1 of 4), 1987 - 1999 (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Management Notebook (2 of 4), 1976 - 1994 (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Management Notebook (3 of 4) (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Management Notebook (4 of 4) (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - Management Notebook (1 of 5), 1985 - 1994 (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - Management Notebook (2 of 5), 1974 - 1990 (Box 168, Folder 11)
    - Management Notebook (3 of 5) (Box 168, Folder 12)
    - American Flag (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Management Notebook (4 of 5), 1981 - 1993 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Management Notebook (5 of 5), 1982 - 1989 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence / Reports (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Bylaws / Policy (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - SPS Correspondence, 1988 - 1993 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Committee Minutes, 1994 - 1996 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Publicity (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Peak Lists (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - 30th Anniversary Issue of Echo, no date available (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1980 - 1988 (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 170, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 170, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1972 - 1973 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Socorro Alpino (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Climbing Route Index, no date available (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Emblem Holders / List Finishers (Box 171, Folder 9)
    - Leader Classification File (Box 171, Folder 10)
    - Safety, 1963 - 1978 (Box 171, Folder 11)
    - For the Scrapbook, [1/16/1959] - [10/1961] (Box 171, Folder 12)
    - SPS Historical Material (Box 171, Folder 13)
    - Past Trips (Box 171, Folder 14)
    - Mountaineers' List, 1970 - 1994 (Box 171, Folder 15)
    - Bylaws Past and Present (1 of 2), 1959 - 1986 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Bylaws Past and Present (2 of 2) (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Membership Info Sheet (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - SPS Membership Lists, 1975 - 1980 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - SPS Membership Lists, 1987 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - SPS Membership Lists (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Semi-Annual Membership Directory (1 of 2) (Box 173, Folder 1)
      Directory is unbound
    - Semi-Annual Membership Directory (2 of 2), 1970 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Guide to the Desert Peaks of the Southwest (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Road and Peak Guide (Second & Third Editions) (Box 180, Folder 5)
      Second edition is a cirrected version of the First edition, no major changes
    - Road and Peak Guide (Fourth Edition), 1998 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Road and Peak Guide (Fifth Edition), 2006 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Road and Peak Guide (Fifth Edition), DPS History & Lore, no date available (Box 181, Folder 3)
      2 CDs.
    - Peaks List (Box 181, Folder 4)
      28th Edition, includes 98 peaks
    - Emblem Holder List, 1995 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Emblem Letters, 1947 - 1982 (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Emblem Letters (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - List Finisher Lists (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - List Finisher Letters, 1983 - 1994 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - List Finisher Records, 1963 - (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Membership Applications (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Membership Letters (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Membership Lists, 1999 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Membership Lists, 1949 - (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Journal - Membership Roll (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Awards (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Bylaws, 1992 (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Bylaws, 1950 - (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - Minutes of Management Committee Meeting (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - Minutes of Meetings (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1947 - 1982 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Peter Preston Artwork, 1978 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Annual Banquet Newsletter (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Photos, 1937 - 1955 (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - Safety Chair, 1990s (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - Duties and Responsibilities (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - Secretary's Reports (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - Insurance, no date available (Box 187, Folder 9)
    - Treasurer Reports, 1967 - 1981 (Box 187, Folder 10)
    - Mountaineering Committee (Box 187, Folder 11)
    - Membership Directory (Box 188, Folder 1)
      Bound directory, box 188 is a flat box
    - Register for mountain, "New York", 1986-2008 (Box 189, Folder 7)
      Water damaged.
    - SPS photographs & logs, Summit Magazine, circa 1960-1980 (Box 207, Folders 1-6)
      CONTAINS UNPROCESSED DIGITAL MATERIALS: Contains DVD with photographs displayed on slides in folder 5. Digital materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email AskLSC@library.ucla.edu.
    - SPS peak registers, circa 1935-2000 (Box 208, Folders 2-5)
    - SPS peak canisters, circa 1935-2000 (Box 209)
    - Sierra cup materials (correspondence, articles, etc.), circa 1973-2013 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Sierra Cup, circa 1940 (Box 209)
    - Bill T. Russell altimeter, circa 1980s (Box 209)
    - Correspondence & organizational documents, 2005-2014 (Box 210, Folders 1-6)
    - Bylaws, correspondence, forms, & insurance information, circa 1980-1999 (Box 211, Folders 1-12)
      CONTAINS UNPROCESSED DIGITAL MATERIALS: Folder 12 contains 7 floppy disks of organizational files. Digital materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email AskLSC@library.ucla.edu.
    - SPS Treasurer's folders, 1998-2000 (Box 214, Folders 1-19)
    - SPS Treasurer's folders, 2001-2002 (Box 215, Folders 1-19)
    - Duane McRuer (former SPS chair) correspondence, forms, and publication drafts, circa 1990s (Box 216, Folders 1-8)
      CONTAINS UNPROCESSED DIGITAL MATERIALS: Box contains 4 unprocessed floppy disks. Digital materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email AskLSC@library.ucla.edu.
    - Duane McRuer (former SPS chair) correspondence and Leadership Reference Book materials, circa 1990s (Box 217, Folders 1-5)
      CONTAINS UNPROCESSED DIGITAL MATERIALS: Box contains 2 unprocessed floppy disks. Digital materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email AskLSC@library.ucla.edu.
    - Register reports & trip documents, 1992-1996 (Box 218, Folders 1-13)
    - Sign up sheets & trip leader materials, 1991-2001 (Box 219, Folders 1-12)
    - Trip documents, 1989-1999 (Box 220, Folders 1-12)
    - Trip documents, correspondence, & trip leader materials, 1994-2000 (Box 221, Folders 1-14)
    - Peak guides & trip journals, 1954-1997 (Box 223, Folders 9-11)
    - Peak registers, circa 1997 (Box 223, Folder 12)
    - Various Chair & Management Committee document binders, 1984-2003 (Box 224, Folders 1-6)
    - Banquet materials & organizational documents, circa 1994-2008 (Box 225, Folders 1-12)
    - SPS membership rosters, 1995-2016 (Box 226, Folder 1)
    - Insurance, forms and list records, 1995-2002 (Box 226, Folders 2-3)
    - Various Echo drafts, circa 1974-2005 (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - SPS photographs, circa 1998-2005 (Box 226, Folders 5-6)
    - Chair notebook, 1997-2000 (Box 227, Folders 1-12)
    - 50th Anniversary Banquet planning binder, 2005 (Box 227, Folder 13)
    - Banquet planning binders, 1996-2002 (Box 228, Folders 1-9)
      CONTAINS UNPROCESSED DIGITAL MATERIALS: Folder 7 contains floppy disk with 2002 Banquet materials. Digital materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email AskLSC@library.ucla.edu.
  - Ski Mountaineers Section
    - Membership Directory, 1948 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Southern California Section
    - Miscellaneous (Box 156, Folder 1)
- Pollution
  - Pollution tax. (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Environmental/Occupational health hazards. (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Hazardous substances. (Box 89, Folder 9-16)
  - Light Pollution. (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Noise. (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Noise control. (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Pesticides. (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Oil pollution. (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Solid waste. (Box 92, Folder 2-4)
  - Thermal pollution. (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Visual pollution (billboards). (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - 19/43-20/1. Water pollution. (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Population
  - Economics of Pollution control. (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Population (general). (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Population. (Box 93, Folder 3-5)
  - Population (Box 94, Folder 1-3)
- Power and Energy
  - Power and Energy (Box 94, Folder 4-7)
  - Power and Energy (Box 95, Folder 1-6)
  - 21/6-10. (Box 96, Folder 1-5)
  - 21/12-18. (Box 97, Folder 1-6)
  - 21/22-24. (Box 98, Folder 1-8)
  - 21/27-34. (Box 99, Folder 1-13)
  - 21/34a-41. (Box 100, Folder 1-5)
  - 21/41-45. (Box 101, Folder 1-7)
  - 21/45-47a. (Box 102, Folder 1-6)
  - 21/47C-55. (Box 103, Folder 1-8)
  - Intermountain west. 21/56-57a. (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Intermountain west (continued) 21/57a-64. (Box 105, Folder 1-7)
  - Intermountain west. 21/64-65. (Box 106, Folder 1-2)
- SCLDF
  - (Various). (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Active docket. (Box 119, Folder 6)
- SCLDF[?]
  - Expense reports. (Box 119, Folder 7)
- SCRCC Minutes, 1951-84
  - 1980-84. (Box 115, Folder 1-5)
  - 1970-79. (Box 115, Folder 6-15)
  - 1960-69. (Box 115, Folder 16-25)
  - 1951-59. (Box 115, Folder 26-34)
  - Roster. (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Financial Status. (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence. (Box 116, Folder 3)
- SCRCC Resolutions, 1964-1974
  - 1965-1974. (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - 1975-. (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - 1951-1964. (Box 116, Folder 6)
- SCRCC Subcommittees, v.d.
  - Air resources. (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - California state parks. (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Coastal condition. (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Coastal TF. (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Desert subcommitee. (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Eastern Sierra Nevada. (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Energy. (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Forest practices. (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Geothermal resources. (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Indian lands. (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - ORV's. (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Owens Valley. (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Pesticides/Herbicides. (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Sheep Mountain wilderness TF. (Box 116, Folder 20)
- Sierra Club - Angeles Chapter
  Archive Transferral to UCLA Special Collections, February 1996.
  - Awards (National). (Box 139)
  - California Coastal Commission. (Box 139)
  - Elections, Chapter. (Box 139)
  - Dinosaul N.M. (Box 139)
  - Diamond Jubilee publications. (Box 139)
  - Diamond Jubilee Newsletters. (Box 139)
  - Anti-Litter Committee (Angeles). (Box 139)